<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Egyszerű fájlkezelő</string>
    <string name="app_launcher_name">Fájlkezelő</string>
    <string name="press_back_again">A kilépéshez nyomja meg újra a vissza gombot</string>
    <string name="go_to_home_folder">Ugrás a kezdőmappára</string>
    <string name="set_as_home_folder">Beállítás kezdőmappának</string>
    <string name="home_folder_updated">Kezdőmappa frissítve</string>
    <string name="copy_path">Útvonal vágólapra másolása</string>
    <string name="path_copied">Útvonal másolva</string>
    <string name="select_audio_file">Válasszon egy hangfájlt</string>
    <string name="search_folder">Mappa keresése</string>
    <string name="rooted_device_only">Ez a művelet csak root jogosultságot támogató eszközökön működik</string>
    <string name="recents">Frissek</string>
    <string name="show_recents">Frissek megjelenítése</string>
    <!-- Open as -->
    <string name="open_as">Megnyitás másként</string>
    <string name="text_file">Szövegfájl</string>
    <string name="image_file">Képfájl</string>
    <string name="audio_file">Hangfájl</string>
    <string name="video_file">Videófájl</string>
    <string name="other_file">Egyéb fájl</string>
    <!-- Compression -->
    <string name="compress">Tömörítés</string>
    <string name="decompress">Kibontás</string>
    <string name="compress_as">Tömörítés másként</string>
    <string name="compressing">Tömörítés…</string>
    <string name="decompressing">Kibontás…</string>
    <string name="compression_successful">Tömörítés sikeres</string>
    <string name="decompression_successful">Kibontás sikeres</string>
    <string name="compressing_failed">Tömörítés sikertelen</string>
    <string name="decompressing_failed">Kibontás sikertelen</string>
    <!-- Favorites -->
    <string name="manage_favorites">Kedvencek kezelése</string>
    <string name="go_to_favorite">Ugrás kedvenchez</string>
    <string name="favorites_activity_placeholder">A gyakran használt mappákat kedvencnek jelölheti, hogy bárhonnan könnyen elérje őket.</string>
    <!-- File Editor -->
    <string name="file_editor">Fájlszerkesztő</string>
    <!-- Storage analysis -->
    <string name="storage_analysis">Tárolóelemzés</string>
    <string name="images">Képek</string>
    <string name="videos">Videók</string>
    <string name="audio">Hangok</string>
    <string name="documents">Dokumentumok</string>
    <string name="downloads">Letöltések</string>
    <string name="archives">Archívumok</string>
    <string name="others">Egyebek</string>
    <string name="storage_free">szabad</string>
    <string name="total_storage">Összes tárhely: %s</string>
    <!-- Settings -->
    <string name="enable_root_access">Root hozzáférés engedélyezése</string>
    <string name="press_back_twice">A Vissza gombot kétszer kelljen megnyomni az alkalmazásból történő kilépéshez</string>
    <!-- Strings displayed only on Google Playstore. Optional, but good to have -->
    <!-- App title has to have less than 50 characters. If you cannot squeeze it, just remove a part of it -->
    <string name="app_title">Egyszerű fájlkezelő Pro – Fájlkezelés könnyedén</string>
    <!-- Short description has to have less than 80 chars -->
    <string name="app_short_description">Egyszerű, reklámmentes fájlkezelő, amely tiszteletben tartja az adatvédelmét</string>
    <string name="app_long_description">
        A lightweight quick file manager for everyday use. It offers a userful search functionality, you can also customize the home folder and select favorite folders for quick access.

        The app contains multiple powerful security related functions, like password protecting hidden items, deleting files, or the whole app. You can choose between using a pattern, pin, or a fingerprint to keep your data private.

        This modern file organizer supports fast browsing of root files, SD cards and USB devices.

        To keep your productive, it obviously has all the standard file operations like rename, copy, move, delete, share etc. It can also be used for saving up some storage, since it allows compressing and decompressing too. You can easily create new files or folders if you wish so.

        You can obviously select sorting by multiple different values, toggle between ascending and descending, or use a folder specific sorting.

        By just a few clicks you can also check file or folder properties, which shows various fields like the file size, date of the last modification, or EXIF values like the creation date, camera model at photos etc.

        To get a file or folders path quickly, you can easily select it by long pressing and copying it in the clipboard.

        You can create handy desktop shortcuts for accessing your favorite items quickly.

        It contains a light file editor that you can use either for printing documents, editing them, or read easily with using zoom gestures, whenever needed.

        It comes with material design and dark theme by default, provides great user experience for easy usage. The lack of internet access gives you more privacy, security and stability than other apps.

        Nincsenek reklámok, sem felesleges engedélykérések. Teljesen nyílt forráskódú. Sötét téma is elérhető.

        <b>Check out the full suite of Simple Tools here:</b>
        https://www.simplemobiletools.com

        <b>Standalone website of Simple File Manager Pro:</b>
        https://www.simplemobiletools.com/filemanager

        <b>Facebook:</b>
        https://www.facebook.com/simplemobiletools

        <b>Reddit:</b>
        https://www.reddit.com/r/SimpleMobileTools
    </string>
    <!--
        Haven't found some strings? There's more at
        https://github.com/SimpleMobileTools/Simple-Commons/tree/master/commons/src/main/res
    -->
</resources>
